[{
    "question": "Which body part does a programmer know best?",
    "answer": "ARM",
    "upvotes": 136,
    "downvotes": 26,
    "id": 1,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Relationship status?",
    "answer": "I'll leave the relations to the database.",
    "upvotes": 87,
    "downvotes": 34,
    "id": 2,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "How do you get the code for the bank vault?",
    "answer": "You checkout their branch.",
    "upvotes": 3,
    "downvotes": 112,
    "id": 3,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "How did the developer announce their engagement?",
    "answer": "They returned true!",
    "upvotes": 81,
    "downvotes": 179,
    "id": 4,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why did the security conscious engineer refuse to pay their dinner bill?",
    "answer": "Because they could not verify the checksum.",
    "upvotes": 136,
    "downvotes": 177,
    "id": 5,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What do you call a busy waiter?",
    "answer": "A server.",
    "upvotes": 106,
    "downvotes": 129,
    "id": 6,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What do you call an idle server?",
    "answer": "A waiter.",
    "upvotes": 107,
    "downvotes": 145,
    "id": 7,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "How many Prolog programmers does it take to change a lightbulb?",
    "answer": "Yes.",
    "upvotes": 8,
    "downvotes": 179,
    "id": 8,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What diet did the ghost developer go on?",
    "answer": "Boolean",
    "upvotes": 86,
    "downvotes": 29,
    "id": 9,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why was the developer unhappy at their job?",
    "answer": "They wanted arrays.",
    "upvotes": 96,
    "downvotes": 8,
    "id": 10,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why was the function sad after a successful first call?",
    "answer": "It didnâ€™t get a callback.",
    "upvotes": 156,
    "downvotes": 45,
    "id": 11,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why did the angry function exceed the callstack size?",
    "answer": "It got into an Argument with itself",
    "upvotes": 56,
    "downvotes": 102,
    "id": 12,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Whats the object-oriented way to become wealthy?",
    "answer": "Inheritance",
    "upvotes": 78,
    "downvotes": 81,
    "id": 13,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why did the developer ground their kid?",
    "answer": "They weren't telling the truthy",
    "upvotes": 174,
    "downvotes": 96,
    "id": 14,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What did the array say after it was extended?",
    "answer": "Stop objectifying me.",
    "upvotes": 56,
    "downvotes": 169,
    "id": 15,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Where did the parallel function wash its hands?",
    "answer": "Async",
    "upvotes": 138,
    "downvotes": 187,
    "id": 16,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why did the functions stop calling each other?",
    "answer": "Because they had constant arguments.",
    "upvotes": 67,
    "downvotes": 125,
    "id": 17,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What's the second movie about a database engineer called?",
    "answer": "The SQL.",
    "upvotes": 56,
    "downvotes": 46,
    "id": 18,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why doesn't Hollywood make more Big Data movies?",
    "answer": "NoSQL.",
    "upvotes": 27,
    "downvotes": 38,
    "id": 19,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What did the spider do on the computer?",
    "answer": "Made a website!",
    "upvotes": 159,
    "downvotes": 64,
    "id": 20,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What did the computer do at lunchtime?",
    "answer": "Had a byte!",
    "upvotes": 51,
    "downvotes": 55,
    "id": 21,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What does a baby computer call his father?",
    "answer": "Data!",
    "upvotes": 118,
    "downvotes": 97,
    "id": 22,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why did the computer keep sneezing?",
    "answer": "It had a virus!",
    "upvotes": 172,
    "downvotes": 95,
    "id": 23,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What is a computer virus?",
    "answer": "A terminal illness!",
    "upvotes": 121,
    "downvotes": 193,
    "id": 24,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why was the computer freezing?",
    "answer": "It left its Windows open!",
    "upvotes": 126,
    "downvotes": 112,
    "id": 25,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why was there a bug in the computer?",
    "answer": "Because it was looking for a byte to eat?",
    "upvotes": 111,
    "downvotes": 75,
    "id": 26,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why did the computer squeak?",
    "answer": "Because someone stepped on its mouse!",
    "upvotes": 25,
    "downvotes": 184,
    "id": 27,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What do you get when you cross a computer and a life guard?",
    "answer": "A screensaver!",
    "upvotes": 124,
    "downvotes": 133,
    "id": 28,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Where do all the cool mice live?",
    "answer": "In their mousepads!",
    "upvotes": 94,
    "downvotes": 39,
    "id": 29,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What do you get when you cross a computer with an elephant?",
    "answer": "Lots of memory!",
    "upvotes": 137,
    "downvotes": 176,
    "id": 30,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "How do programming pirates pass method parameters?",
    "answer": "Varrrrarrrgs.",
    "upvotes": 146,
    "downvotes": 175,
    "id": 31,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "How do programming shepherds count their flock?",
    "answer": "With lambda functions",
    "upvotes": 122,
    "downvotes": 113,
    "id": 32,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What airline do developers prefer when they're in a rush?",
    "answer": "Delta.",
    "upvotes": 87,
    "downvotes": 195,
    "id": 33,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "How did pirates collaborate before computers ?",
    "answer": "Pier to pier networking.",
    "upvotes": 105,
    "downvotes": 13,
    "id": 34,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why don't bachelors like Git?",
    "answer": "Because they are afraid to commit.",
    "upvotes": 154,
    "downvotes": 87,
    "id": 35,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why was the developer's family upset with them at dinner?",
    "answer": "They forgot to git squash before going home",
    "upvotes": 121,
    "downvotes": 140,
    "id": 36,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What did JavaScript call his son?",
    "answer": "JSON!",
    "upvotes": 19,
    "downvotes": 99,
    "id": 37,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What did the proud React component say to its child?",
    "answer": "I've got to give you props",
    "upvotes": 117,
    "downvotes": 144,
    "id": 38,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What did the server say to his client who was having a bad day?",
    "answer": "Everything's going to be 200",
    "upvotes": 13,
    "downvotes": 18,
    "id": 39,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why did the developer go broke?",
    "answer": "Because they used up all their cache",
    "upvotes": 55,
    "downvotes": 40,
    "id": 40,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Are computers dangerous?",
    "answer": "Nah, they don't byte. They just nibble a bit.",
    "upvotes": 141,
    "downvotes": 58,
    "id": 41,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "How did the mafioso kill the Node server?",
    "answer": "Tie await to it and let it async.",
    "upvotes": 109,
    "downvotes": 31,
    "id": 42,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "You know what the best thing about booleans is?",
    "answer": "Even if you are wrong, you are only off by a bit.",
    "upvotes": 109,
    "downvotes": 127,
    "id": 43,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why do UPS drivers get nervous when their internet is unstable?",
    "answer": "Because they might lose packets.",
    "upvotes": 87,
    "downvotes": 70,
    "id": 44,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why couldnâ€™t the user update a file on a shared server?",
    "answer": "They didnâ€™t have the write permissions",
    "upvotes": 61,
    "downvotes": 91,
    "id": 45,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What do you do when you can't understand your husband's behavior?",
    "answer": "man man",
    "upvotes": 184,
    "downvotes": 176,
    "id": 46,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What do you call a doctor who fixes websites?",
    "answer": "A URLogist",
    "upvotes": 130,
    "downvotes": 115,
    "id": 47,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "How many developers does it take to change a light bulb?",
    "answer": "None. It's a hardware issue",
    "upvotes": 48,
    "downvotes": 61,
    "id": 48,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why do programmers always mix up Halloween and Christmas?",
    "answer": "Because 31 OCT == 25 DEC",
    "upvotes": 100,
    "downvotes": 175,
    "id": 49,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why do kayakers make bad programmers?",
    "answer": "Because they're afraid of waterfall.",
    "upvotes": 44,
    "downvotes": 132,
    "id": 50,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What are computers' favorite snacks?",
    "answer": "Microchips, phish sticks, and cookies. But just a few bytes of each.",
    "upvotes": 122,
    "downvotes": 83,
    "id": 51,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What do computers love to do at the beach?",
    "answer": "Put on some spam block for protection so they can safely surf the net while catching some .WAVs!",
    "upvotes": 40,
    "downvotes": 25,
    "id": 52,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What do you call a computer that sings?",
    "answer": "A-dell.",
    "upvotes": 79,
    "downvotes": 70,
    "id": 53,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What's a compiler developer's favorite spice?",
    "answer": "Parsley.",
    "upvotes": 171,
    "downvotes": 140,
    "id": 54,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "When do front end developers go out to eat?",
    "answer": "On their lunch `<br>`.",
    "upvotes": 148,
    "downvotes": 87,
    "id": 55,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "How do you help JS errors?",
    "answer": "You `console` them!",
    "upvotes": 48,
    "downvotes": 23,
    "id": 56,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why don't parents teach their kids about regular expressions?",
    "answer": "Because they don't want them playing with matches",
    "upvotes": 116,
    "downvotes": 155,
    "id": 57,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why didn't the `<div />` get invited to the dinner party?",
    "answer": "Because it had no class!",
    "upvotes": 88,
    "downvotes": 45,
    "id": 58,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why aren't cryptocurrency engineers allowed to vote?",
    "answer": "Because they're miners!",
    "upvotes": 83,
    "downvotes": 187,
    "id": 59,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why did the constant break up with the variable?",
    "answer": "Because they changed.",
    "upvotes": 125,
    "downvotes": 71,
    "id": 60,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why did the database administrator leave his wife?",
    "answer": "She had one-to-many relationships.",
    "upvotes": 178,
    "downvotes": 88,
    "id": 61,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What did the Class say in court when put on trial?",
    "answer": "I strongly object!",
    "upvotes": 70,
    "downvotes": 126,
    "id": 62,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why do Java developers wear glasses?",
    "answer": "Because they don't C#!",
    "upvotes": 112,
    "downvotes": 14,
    "id": 63,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What are the three hardest problems in computer science?",
    "answer": "Naming things and off-by-one errors",
    "upvotes": 165,
    "downvotes": 123,
    "id": 64,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What did the fruit basket say to the developer?",
    "answer": "I hope you're ready for some pear programming!",
    "upvotes": 149,
    "downvotes": 169,
    "id": 65,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "How does a sysadmin keep a fire going?",
    "answer": "They rotate the logs.",
    "upvotes": 84,
    "downvotes": 44,
    "id": 66,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "I love you and I only love you. Does that turn you on?",
    "answer": "AND GATE: No.",
    "upvotes": 50,
    "downvotes": 167,
    "id": 67,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why do all HTML emails get blocked?",
    "answer": "Because they are all `<span />`.",
    "upvotes": 128,
    "downvotes": 57,
    "id": 68,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What did the process say after working in an infinite loop all day?",
    "answer": "I need a break.",
    "upvotes": 37,
    "downvotes": 130,
    "id": 69,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "An Agent died unexpectedly. How was the crime solved?",
    "answer": "By looking at the Stack Trace.",
    "upvotes": 123,
    "downvotes": 31,
    "id": 70,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why did the document store go out of business?",
    "answer": "It had NoSQL.",
    "upvotes": 64,
    "downvotes": 62,
    "id": 71,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why can't SQL and NoSQL Developers date one other?",
    "answer": "Because they don't agree on relationships.",
    "upvotes": 8,
    "downvotes": 62,
    "id": 72,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why is Python like the Soviet Union?",
    "answer": "Because it has no private fields",
    "upvotes": 29,
    "downvotes": 132,
    "id": 73,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Where did the API go to eat?",
    "answer": "To the RESTaurant",
    "upvotes": 96,
    "downvotes": 89,
    "id": 74,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why shouldn't you trust Matlab developers?",
    "answer": "Because they're always plotting something.",
    "upvotes": 44,
    "downvotes": 93,
    "id": 75,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why did the developer have to quit smoking?",
    "answer": "Because they couldn't afford to pay the new syntax.",
    "upvotes": 13,
    "downvotes": 78,
    "id": 76,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "How does a programmer open a jar for their significant other?",
    "answer": "They install Java",
    "upvotes": 191,
    "downvotes": 50,
    "id": 77,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What did the psychic say to the developers?",
    "answer": "I see dev people.",
    "upvotes": 135,
    "downvotes": 139,
    "id": 78,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Where does the pirate stash all of their digital treasures?",
    "answer": "RAR",
    "upvotes": 120,
    "downvotes": 53,
    "id": 79,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What is React's favorite movie genre?",
    "answer": "Suspense",
    "upvotes": 50,
    "downvotes": 110,
    "id": 80,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why couldn't the React component understand the joke?",
    "answer": "Because it didn't get the context.",
    "upvotes": 141,
    "downvotes": 44,
    "id": 81,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What did XHR say to AJAX when it thought it was being a Mean Girl?",
    "answer": "Stop trying to make fetch happen!",
    "upvotes": 73,
    "downvotes": 98,
    "id": 82,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What was Grace Hopper's favorite car?",
    "answer": "VW Bug",
    "upvotes": 85,
    "downvotes": 175,
    "id": 83,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What is a pirate's favorite programming language?",
    "answer": "You'd think it was R, but a pirate's first love is Objectively C.",
    "upvotes": 59,
    "downvotes": 106,
    "id": 84,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why did the programmer come home crying?",
    "answer": "His friends were always boolean him.",
    "upvotes": 16,
    "downvotes": 102,
    "id": 85,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What PostgreSQL library should Python developers use for adult-oriented code?",
    "answer": "psycoPG13",
    "upvotes": 36,
    "downvotes": 15,
    "id": 86,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What do you call a beverage that is 75% Root Beer, and 75% Ice Cream?",
    "answer": "A Float",
    "upvotes": 88,
    "downvotes": 53,
    "id": 87,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What accommodations did the JavaScript developer request at the hotel?",
    "answer": "A room with a Vue.",
    "upvotes": 89,
    "downvotes": 39,
    "id": 88,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Where do developers drink?",
    "answer": "The Foo bar",
    "upvotes": 24,
    "downvotes": 100,
    "id": 89,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why was the engineer upset when the bartender served them `1` shot of whiskey?",
    "answer": "Because they thought they ordered a double.",
    "upvotes": 0,
    "downvotes": 38,
    "id": 90,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why do assembly programmers need to know how to swim?",
    "answer": "Because they work below C level.",
    "upvotes": 49,
    "downvotes": 127,
    "id": 91,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Who used the internet before it was cool?",
    "answer": "Httpsters",
    "upvotes": 89,
    "downvotes": 23,
    "id": 92,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What kind of computer can hold a musical note?",
    "answer": "A Dell.",
    "upvotes": 170,
    "downvotes": 154,
    "id": 93,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why did the web developer always go to the wrong hotel room?",
    "answer": "They were in room 301.",
    "upvotes": 27,
    "downvotes": 147,
    "id": 94,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "How do you stop a web developer stealing your stuff?",
    "answer": "Write 403 on it.",
    "upvotes": 61,
    "downvotes": 43,
    "id": 95,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why are machine learning models so fit?",
    "answer": "Because they do weight training.",
    "upvotes": 125,
    "downvotes": 134,
    "id": 96,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why did Gargamel shut down the internet?",
    "answer": "Because he didn't want people **SMURFING** the web!",
    "upvotes": 144,
    "downvotes": 41,
    "id": 97,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What did the command line die of?",
    "answer": "A Terminal illness.",
    "upvotes": 45,
    "downvotes": 182,
    "id": 98,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Did you hear what the clumsy cryptographer did to their password?",
    "answer": "Made a hash of it.",
    "upvotes": 94,
    "downvotes": 115,
    "id": 99,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why are keyboards always working so hard?",
    "answer": "Cause they have two shifts!",
    "upvotes": 81,
    "downvotes": 124,
    "id": 100,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What are clouds made of?",
    "answer": "Mostly linux servers.",
    "upvotes": 46,
    "downvotes": 47,
    "id": 101,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why did Tom Selleck never git commit anything?",
    "answer": "Because he thought he mustache his work.",
    "upvotes": 94,
    "downvotes": 86,
    "id": 102,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "How does Mr. Potato Head (dev edition 0.0.1) remove his mustache?",
    "answer": "git stache pop",
    "upvotes": 87,
    "downvotes": 28,
    "id": 103,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why can't you use 'Soup' as your password?",
    "answer": "Because it isn't `stroganoff`",
    "upvotes": 198,
    "downvotes": 28,
    "id": 104,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why do developers use mechanical keyboards?",
    "answer": "To strongly type their code.",
    "upvotes": 189,
    "downvotes": 57,
    "id": 105,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What is a developer's favorite country song?",
    "answer": "Hello World - by Lady Antebellum",
    "upvotes": 1,
    "downvotes": 132,
    "id": 106,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why was nobody given food at the developer conference?",
    "answer": "It was a serverless function!",
    "upvotes": 27,
    "downvotes": 41,
    "id": 107,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why did the developer cancel their dinner plans?",
    "answer": "They were unable to fulfil peer dependencies",
    "upvotes": 171,
    "downvotes": 161,
    "id": 108,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why did the functional programmer finally move out of their house?",
    "answer": "For(e) closure",
    "upvotes": 125,
    "downvotes": 165,
    "id": 109,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "How do JavaScript developers break up?",
    "answer": "They always promise to callback",
    "upvotes": 13,
    "downvotes": 10,
    "id": 110,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why do developers mixup Terminals and Polygraphs?",
    "answer": "Because they both can see a lie (CLI)",
    "upvotes": 156,
    "downvotes": 184,
    "id": 111,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Did you hear about the programmer that was scared of IDEs?",
    "answer": "They retreated back into their shell",
    "upvotes": 171,
    "downvotes": 163,
    "id": 112,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What do you call optimistic front-end developers?",
    "answer": "Stack half-full developers.",
    "upvotes": 8,
    "downvotes": 12,
    "id": 113,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Have you heard the one about the Corduroy pillow?",
    "answer": "It's making HEADLINES!",
    "upvotes": 3,
    "downvotes": 190,
    "id": 114,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Hey officer! How did the hackers escape?",
    "answer": "No idea. They just ransomware.",
    "upvotes": 158,
    "downvotes": 199,
    "id": 115,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why canâ€™t data engineers become hat makers?",
    "answer": "They can only guarantee two thirds of a CAP!",
    "upvotes": 108,
    "downvotes": 91,
    "id": 116,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "How did the hippie learn about database transactions?",
    "answer": "By taking ACID",
    "upvotes": 133,
    "downvotes": 141,
    "id": 117,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why is it called the Dark Ages?",
    "answer": "There were a lot of KNIGHTS!",
    "upvotes": 4,
    "downvotes": 162,
    "id": 118,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What did the Network Administrator say when they caught a nasty virus?",
    "answer": "It hurts when IP",
    "upvotes": 68,
    "downvotes": 62,
    "id": 119,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Which programming language is the shortest?",
    "answer": "HTML. Because it doesn't have a neck between its `<head>` and `<body>`.",
    "upvotes": 78,
    "downvotes": 38,
    "id": 120,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What good can come of 2989 witches casting a hex?",
    "answer": "None, it is always 0xBAD",
    "upvotes": 156,
    "downvotes": 30,
    "id": 121,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Did you hear about the witch who was off by two when casting a hex?",
    "answer": "They failed to make the target DEAD and made them DEAF instead!",
    "upvotes": 72,
    "downvotes": 190,
    "id": 122,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why do Front-End Developers eat lunch alone?",
    "answer": "Because, they don't know how to join tables.",
    "upvotes": 136,
    "downvotes": 65,
    "id": 123,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What advice do you give to a JS developer who has never played baseball?",
    "answer": "Try catch.",
    "upvotes": 147,
    "downvotes": 120,
    "id": 124,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Got any funny DNS jokes?",
    "answer": "Yeah, but it may take 24 hours to get it.",
    "upvotes": 89,
    "downvotes": 27,
    "id": 125,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why were A & B so frustrated?",
    "answer": "Because they couldnâ€™t cdâ€¦",
    "upvotes": 137,
    "downvotes": 70,
    "id": 126,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Where do programmer dad's store their jokes?",
    "answer": "In a dad-a-base.",
    "upvotes": 67,
    "downvotes": 57,
    "id": 127,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why do Websockets make the best therapists?",
    "answer": "They are always listening.",
    "upvotes": 107,
    "downvotes": 137,
    "id": 128,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What kind of image saved the day?",
    "answer": "The HERO image!",
    "upvotes": 186,
    "downvotes": 159,
    "id": 129,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why do programmers prefer dark mode?",
    "answer": "Because light attracts bugs!",
    "upvotes": 115,
    "downvotes": 58,
    "id": 130,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Does this vaccine contain a microchip?",
    "answer": "I don't know for sure, but it must be ARM based.",
    "upvotes": 106,
    "downvotes": 128,
    "id": 131,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "How do you make a 4D Printer?",
    "answer": "Take a 3D printer and give it some time",
    "upvotes": 159,
    "downvotes": 109,
    "id": 132,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "How do front end devs like their brownies?",
    "answer": "GUI",
    "upvotes": 141,
    "downvotes": 170,
    "id": 133,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What do hackers do on a boat?",
    "answer": "Phishing.",
    "upvotes": 49,
    "downvotes": 133,
    "id": 134,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What is the most used language in programming?",
    "answer": "Profanity",
    "upvotes": 53,
    "downvotes": 192,
    "id": 135,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "Why couldn't the HTML list be trusted?",
    "answer": "There were LI's everywhere",
    "upvotes": 75,
    "downvotes": 118,
    "id": 136,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
},
{
    "question": "What do you call a bee that lives in America?",
    "answer": "A USB",
    "upvotes": 157,
    "downvotes": 90,
    "id": 137,
    "author": {"username": "creator", "password":"main", "email": "main@mmm.com", "id": 2, "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"},
    "created_at": "2019-02-03 10:08:02"
}
]